-I'm so sorry. I'm really sorry.   -You're not that sorry.
-真的很对不起   真的真的   -你不需要道歉
I'm really really sorry. ​
真的很对不起
Don't give me a hard time. Give me a break.
别让我为难好吗   让我歇会儿
-Come on! Come on!   -I'm sorry.   -Help! Help!   -I'm...
-拜托   拜托   -对不起   -救救我   -我
-I'm sorry.
-对不起
You know I wasn't drunk.
你知道吗   我没醉
What do you mean you are not drunk?
什么叫你没醉
When I walked in front of that car.
当我在那辆车前走的时候
What car?
什么车
I stepped right out in front of it.
我直接就走到了它前面
I'd never been more sober in my life.
我一生中从没这么清醒过
Go to sleep.
睡觉去吧
Couldn't even get that right, could I?
我连这都做不好   不是吗
If at first you don't succeed, try, try again.
如果你开始没成功   再试试
Go to sleep.
去睡觉吧
I'm proud of you, Vincent.
我为你感到骄傲   Vincent
You must be drunk to call me Vincent.
你一定是喝醉了才叫我Vincent